Iris Kotsinas **ENGINEERING STUDENT**



PERSONAL

Name Iris Kotsinas

Birthday November 21, 1997

Nationality Swedish

Language Swedish, English,

(Spanish, Chinese)

ABOUT ME

I am an active and ambitious, 23-year old, final year Master of Science student with a great interest in game and software development. I strive to apply and develop my programming skills, and I am always open for the opportunity to learn something new.

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

C++, C#, OPENGL, PYTHON, JAVA, TYPESCRIPT/JAVASCRIPT, PHP, SQL, GRAPHQL, NEXT.JS, REACT, VUE, CSS/HTML, UNITY

LINKS

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/iriskotsinas/ Portfolio: iriskotsinas.github.io GitHub: github.com/iriskotsinas

CONTACT

Mobile +46 735 108 508 **Email** iris.kotsinas@gmail.com

Address Nygatan 61

602 34 Norrköping

EDUCATION

Linköping University

Norrköping, SE - M.Sc. in Media Technology and Engineering 2017 - present

Programming, computer graphics, visualization and design.

Relevant selected courses

3D-Computer Graphics	TNM061
Modelling and simulation	TNG022
Practical Data Visualization and Virtual Reality	/ TNM094
Advanced Global Illumination and Rendering	TNGC15
Machine Learning for Social Media	TNM108
Information Visualization	TNM048
Modelling and Animation	TNM079
Artificial Intelligence Principles and Technique	s TNM096
Design and Programming of Computer Game	s TDDD23

Eastern High School

Louisville, KY, USA - High School Exchange Year - STS 2014-2015

Danderyds Gymnasium (High School) Stockholm, SE 2013-2017

- Science program, international focus

EXPERIENCE

We Know IT Sweden AB Linköping, SE - Software Developer 2021/01 - present

Part-time consultant at We Know IT, a student-run IT-consultancy firm (TypeScript, Next.js, Strapi.js)

Upsales Nordic AB Linköping, SE - System Developer 2021/06 - 2021/08

Extended Upsales' booking system, Easy Booking (TypeScript, React, Node.js, MySQL)

Netlight Consulting AB Stockholm, SE

2020/09 - 2021/06

Norrköping, SE

2019/11 - 2020/01

2019

- Student Brand Manager Promoted and created Netlight events for students at Linköping University

Linköping University

- Teaching Assistant, Applied Transform Theory	2021/01 - 2021-03
Assisted students in the course TNG032 Applied Transform Theory (MATLAB)	2020/01 - 2020/03
- Teaching Assistant, Electronic Publishing	2020/11 - 2021/01

Assisted students in the course TNMK30 Electronic Publishing (HTML, PHP, JavaScript, CSS and MySQL)

Axis Communications AB Linköping, SE

- Software Developer Intern 2020/06 - 2020/08 Developed a software for Axis surveillance cameras

(TypeScript, Next.js, mongoose, Express, Docker and more)

EXTRACURRICULAR EXPERIENCE

LiTHehack - Programming mentor	2020-2021
Media Technology Days 2020 - Economy manager	2019-2020
Norrköpings Akademiska Förening för Idrott - Sponsorship manager	2019-2020
Women's association Mette - Economy manager	2018-2019

Swedish women's national lacrosse team

Available on request.

REFERENCES

- Player